<resources>
    <string name="applovin_sdk_key">applovin_sdk_key</string>
    <string name="first_check">I understand that sharing of inappropriate content will not be tolerated.</string>
    <string name="generate_nwatch_an_ad">Generate AI Image</string>
    <string name="policy">https://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/live/3df33ce1-1276-4ee9-8237-12a294f1da76</string>
    <string name="get">Get</string>
    <string name="get_pro">Get PRO</string>
    <string name="gta">GTA</string>
    <string name="hd_images">HD images</string>
    <string name="second_check">I confirm that Im 18 years old or above.</string>
    <string name="see_all">see all</string>
    <string name="select_language">Select language</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="share_your_art_with_the_world">Share your art with the world</string>
    <string name="sorry">Sorry!</string>
    <string name="spinners">Spinners</string>
    <string name="chip_text">Chip text</string>
    <string name="choose_setting">Choose Setting</string>
    <string name="clear_text_end_icon_content_description">Clear text</string>
    <string name="clickforprivacy">By Clicking \'Get Started\'. You are agree to above Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. </string>
    <string name="anime_v2">ANIME V2</string>
    <string name="app_desc">ImageAI AI Art Generator create beautiful art using the power of words with our AI art generator, Imagine AI</string>
    <string name="app_name">ImageAI AI Art Generator</string>
    <string name="unleash_your_imagination_s_power">Unleash Your Imaginations Power.</string>
    <string name="trending">Trending</string>
    <string name="try_now">Try Now</string>
    <string name="trytext">Try</string>
    <string name="ai_character">AI Character</string>
    <string name="ai_edit_images">AI Edit Images</string>
    <string name="ai_fashion">AI Fashion</string>
    <string name="ai_image">AI Image</string>
    <string name="ai_photorealism">AI Photorealism</string>
    <string name="ai_tools">AI Tools</string>
    <string name="let_s_try_different_fashion">let’s try different fashion</string>
    <string name="let_s_try_different_style">let’s try different style....</string>
    <string name="life_time">Life Time</string>
    <string name="absolute_reality">Absolute Reality</string>
    <string name="access">Access</string>
    <string name="add_image">Add Image</string>
    <string name="advance_ai_spinners">Advance AI Spinners</string>
    <string name="advance_settings">Advance Settings</string>
    <string name="advanced_settings">Advanced Settings</string>
    <string name="ai_advance">AI Advance</string>
    <string name="ai_art">AI Art</string>
    <string name="consistency">Consistency</string>
    <string name="continue_">Continue</string>
    <string name="copy_toast_msg">Link copied to clipboard</string>
    <string name="cosmic">COSMIC</string>
    <string name="dark_sushi">Dark Sushi</string>
    <string name="deep_dive">Deep Dive</string>
    <string name="dream_shaper">Dream Shaper</string>
    <string name="enter_prompt">Enter Prompt</string>
    <string name="error_a11y_label">Error: invalid</string>
    <string name="error_icon_content_description">Error</string>
    <string name="euphoric">EUPHORIC</string>
    <string name="aspect_ratio">Aspect Ratio</string>
    <string name="aspect_ratios">Aspect ratios</string>
    <string name="model">Model</string>
    <string name="model_and_style">Model and style</string>
    <string name="monthly">Monthly</string>
    <string name="more_apps">More Apps</string>
    <string name="fantasy">FANTASY</string>
    <string name="fast_amp_high">Fast &amp; High</string>
    <string name="faster_processing">Faster processing</string>
    <string name="fcm_fallback_notification_channel_label">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="hide_bottom_view_on_scroll_behavior">com.google.android.material.behavior.HideBottomViewOnScrollBehavior</string>
    <string name="icon_content_description">Dialog Icon</string>
    <string name="image_remix">Image Remix</string>
    <string name="inspiration">Inspiration</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_exit">Are you sure you want to Exit ?</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="text_homefrag_prompt">Avengers but Coffee Baristas: Serve up a super-powered cup of joe as the Avengers become talented coffee baristas in a realistic coffee shop setting.</string>
    <string name="style">Style</string>
    <string name="styles">Styles</string>
    <string name="watch_an_ad">watch an ad</string>
    <string name="weekly">Weekly</string>
    <string name="year">Year</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="you_can_upload_your_photos_and_use_nprompts_to_make_dramatic_changes_to_your_nimages">You can upload your photos and use\nprompts to make dramatic changes to your\nimages</string>
    <string name="rate_app">Rate App</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="update_app">Update App</string>
    <string name="upload_image">Upload Image</string>
    <string name="original">Original</string>
    <string name="negative_prompt">Negative prompt</string>
    <string name="no_watermark">No watermark</string>
    <string name="item_character_10_text">Art made by Daniel F Gerhartz, Victor Miller-Gausa, Antonio Manzanedo, of main character of Disenchantment princess Tiabeanie Mariabeanie de la Rochambeaux Grunkwitz as known as Bean, disheveled white hair, tight light blue shirt and brown pants, portrait, cinematic lighting, concept photoart, 32k, photoshoot on the throne, unbelievable full length portrait, dark grading undertones, cinematic lighting, hyper detailed, realistic, figurative painter with intricate details, divine proportion, sharp focus, Mysterious</string>
    <string name="item_character_11_text">Portrait of a very beautiful girl in the image of the Joker in the style of Christopher Nolan, Women batman costume, an evil grin on her face, looking into a broken mirror, there is an atmosphere of horror and fear around, you can see a beautiful body, professional photo, high detail, attention to detail, in the style of wallpaper, realism, pearl illusion, cyberpunk, fashion trends, 3s material, HD, detail performance, c4d, 3D, octane rendering, ray tracing, complex details, animated lighting,</string>
    <string name="item_character_12_text">Spider man in dynamics, highly detailed, packed with hidden details, style, high dynamic range, hyper realistic, realistic attention to detail, highly detailed, 32K, intense close - ups, uhd image, realism, colorful realism,</string>
    <string name="item_character_13_text">girl posing in Shibuya for a photo shoot, detailed anime style face, manga style drawing, highly detailed face, pretty facial features, 2d, hand drawn, digital drawing of a manga character, fashionable modern clothing, trendy Instagram influencer, Tokyo street style, dynamic pose, bright lighting, anime character portrait</string>
    <string name="item_character_14_text">(best quality,ultra-detalhado),centered,(Realistic) Raphtalia, (anime),(retrato),(vermelho e branco),(clear lighting),(armaduras e armas detalhadas), (fierce expression),(Intensa cena de batalha),(fantasia),(Olhos determinados),(flowing hair),(foco nítido),(vivid colors),(magic effects),(heroic),(epics),(emocional),(cativante),(master part:1.2)</string>
    <string name="item_character_15_text">In the bustling city of Central City, a bolt of lightning strikes the laboratory of Barry Allen, a brilliant forensic scientist. Suddenly, he finds himself transformed into the fastest man alive, the Scarlet Speedster known as The Flash. With his red suit and lightning bolt emblem, he races against time to protect his city from criminals and metahuman threats. As he hurtles through the streets, he leaves a trail of lightning in his wake, embodying the very essence of speed itself. But behind the mask, Barry Allen grapples with the responsibilities of his dual life and the eternal quest for answers about his newfound powers. The Flash adventures are a whirlwind of excitement, justice, and the eternal pursuit of truth, intricate design and details, dramatic lighting, hyperrealism, photorealistic, cinematic, 8k</string>
    <string name="item_character_16_text">A detailed art portrait of Squall Leonhart, Final fantasy VIII, intricate details, 4k, sharp focus, photo realistic, luis royo, H. R. Giger</string>
    <string name="item_character_17_text">HDR photo of A photo of a slender anime girl with petite bust, toned abs, standing in gym, with photo-realistic style, crisp lines, vibrant colors, highlighting her beauty. . High dynamic range, vivid, rich details, clear shadows and highlights, realistic, intense, enhanced contrast, highly detailed</string>
    <string name="item_character_18_text">A portrait of a female final fantasy ethereal character figure in the realm of fantasy, muscular and well-built physique, with piercing eyes, exudes an aura of power and strength, shiny metal armor, skilled in swordsmanship, able to wield a sword with precision and speed, has a natural affinity for nature magic, She can communicate with animals, control plants, and summon natural elements to aid her in battle, highly detailed, 8k resolution, smooth, in focus, photo realistic, finely detailed</string>
    <string name="item_character_1_text">Bare skin, apron, kitchen, cooking, cutting, long hair, hair, smooth hair, blonde hair, European, blissful, happy, robot, mechanical, artificial, natural, soothing, warming, Caucasian, detailed face, highly detailed, intricate details, symmetrical, digital 3d, hard surface, real-time, vfx, volumetric lighting, ambient light, ultra hd, hdr, soft, well proportioned</string>
    <string name="item_character_2_text">Imagine a woman handcrafted by the Gods: She emerging from molten lava, levitating above the heart of a volcano. She in a otherworldly dress made by fire and ashes that shapes her body perfectly. Her face resembles of a beautiful woman with some magical elements. Her hair is fiery red and is fueled by the very energy of life itself, a throwback to The Creation at the same time connecting with today nature. Every element of this portrait should come together naturally creating that most beautiful concept art ever created.</string>
    <string name="item_character_3_text">studio lighting, film, movie scene, extreme detail, 12k, masterpiece, hyperrealistic, realistic, Krillin from Dragon Ball going super saiyan, Canon EOS R6 Mark II, fiery particles in the air, smoke in the background, void, cell shaded, (detailed hands), golden eyebrows, blue eyes, detailed fingers, detailed muscles, anatomically correct, left palm outstretched and firing a blast of energy</string>
    <string name="item_character_4_text">McDonald’s as a villain in mortal kombat, hyper realistic</string>
    <string name="item_character_5_text">Art in fantasy Anime Style Painter action effect, sharp focus, studio photo, masterpiece, UHD</string>
    <string name="item_character_6_text">male apache warrior figure in war derss with war bonnets headdress, feirce, face painted, armed figure, dual wielding axe, intricate native Indian outfit, intricate details, ornate cinematic lighting, high definition, high details, focused, unreal engine 5, cinematic, depth of field, on battleground environment, photography, dramatic light, natural light, photorealism, real shadow, soft illumination, ray tracing, cinematic rendering, 8K, vfx post production, rtx tracing lighting, octane rendering</string>
    <string name="item_character_7_text">The Joker, a villain from the Batman film series, looks at himself in a broken mirror, in the style of Christopher Nolan, in dynamic, atmosphere of darkness and horror, dramatic light, highly detailed, packed with hidden details, hyper realistic, in the style of illusory wallpaper portraits, colorful realism, realistic attention to detail, highly detailed, intense close - ups, uhd image, realism, colorful realism, UHD, 8K</string>
    <string name="item_character_8_text">Hyperrealistic full-length portrait of a futuristic cyberpunk hacker | in a neon-lit cyber alley | detailed techno-enhanced face!! | full body!! | cyberpunk attire | holographic interfaces | intricate | tech-savvy | realistic | hyperrealistic | cinematic | character design | concept art | highly detailed | illustration | digital art | digital painting | depth of field, photorealism, half-human, half-robotic tattoo,</string>
    <string name="item_character_9_text">a man in a superman suit standing in a dark room, a hologram by Zack Snyder, featured on cg society, superflat, reimagined by industrial light and magic, dc comics, anamorphic lens flare</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_10_text">Photo of a cartoon-like penguin with a top hat that is on the roof of a building abandoned with vegetation, watching the sunset that can be seen on the horizon. In pixel art style.</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_11_text">a beautiful girl face wearing sunglasses and red lipstick, a lifelike portrait with every pore and strand of hair visible, Combine multiple images to create a surreal and visually stunning composition, art nouveau.</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_12_text">a realistic vintage car adorned with an intricate, graffiti-style mural, full wide view, highly detailed, 8</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_13_text">The image features a stunningly beautiful young France girl who is talking on her cell phone while standing on the street. She is wearing a white top. She is also wearing jeans and glasses, and she is smiling as she engages in her phone conversation. (controlnet_mode:canny, juggernautXL_v5, sdxl-1. 0. 0. 9. safetensors, SeargeSDXL4.1-Llama2 prompt generator)</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_14_text">The picture features a 18 years of girl wearing a suit and tie, standing in front of a wall. She is posing for the camera, and her outfit includes a white shirt and a red tie. The woman appears to be confident and well-dressed, possibly for a professional or formal occasion. The image is in black and white, which adds a classic and timeless feel to the scene. (controlnet_mode:canny, juggernautXL_v5, sdxl-1. 0. 0. 9. safetensors, SeargeSDXL4.1-Llama2 prompt generator)</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_15_text">Beautiful girl fitness trainer, stands and shows her perfect figure to her full height, well - developed body, beautiful body, athletic legs and hips, colorful realism, epic light, modularity, Highest quality, perfect masterpiece, perfect art, 8K,young and energetic girl, cyberpunk, fashion trends, 3s material, HD, detail performance, ray tracing, complex details, animated lighting, OCrenderer, 8k,</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_16_text">cute 18yo, innocent look, shy, delicate, seductive smirk, lip bite, black nails, eyeliner</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_17_text">Realistic Ryuk from Death Note with tattoos, (detailed stunning environment), cinematic, cover art, (low front angle), view Ryuk with tattoos, highly detailed, smooth, sharp focus, cinematic lighting, atmospheric, photoreal, 8k, Canon EF 200–400mm f/4L IS USM Extender 1. 4x Lens, stan Winston studio</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_18_text">A visual stunning full body photography of a female soccer player, stadium, volumetric lighting, volumetric atmosphere, centered| intricate| highly detailed| breathtaking beauty| precise lineart| vibrant| comprehensive cinematic| Sandra Chevrier, Anna Dittmann, dynamic pose, pretty hands, beautiful face</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_1_text">A photo of a beautiful cyborg female angel, with expressionless facial features, heavenly, long blonde hair, white armor, melancholy, dynamic lighting, dark background, &lt;lora:ClassipeintXL1.9:1&gt;</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_2_text">a woman with tattoos and piercings wearing a black shirt, a 3D render by Sam Spratt, cgsociety, photorealism, daz3d, zbrush, rendered in maya</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_3_text">a woman in a shiny jacket posing for a picture, cyberpunk art by Lü Ji, trending on cg society, retrofuturism, glowing neon, futuristic, synthwave</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_4_text">studio lighting, film, movie scene, extreme detail, 12k, masterpiece, hyperrealistic, realistic, Peter Quill (Chris Pratt) from Guardians of the Galaxy holding an infinity stone, glowing eyes, powerful shot, Canon EOS R6 Mark II, depth of field, mystical purple particles floating in the air, swirls of power, small purple gem</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_5_text">female wolf character portrait with long hair and a large eye, in the style of sculptural costumes, solarization effect, light white and light indigo, matte photo, photo-realistic techniques, fawncore, monochromatic white figures, detailed matte painting, deep color, fantastical, intricate detail, splash screen, complementary colors, fantasy concept art, 8k resolution trending on Artstation Unreal Engine 5</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_6_text">a man in a helmet with a dragon on his head, an airbrush painting by Raymond Swanland, featured on zbrush central, fantasy art, reimagined by industrial light and magic, detailed painting, behance hd</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_7_text">Rem, Re:Zero, head and shoulders portrait, 8k resolution concept art portrait by Greg Rutkowski, Artgerm, WLOP, Alphonse Mucha dynamic lighting hyperdetailed intricately detailed Splash art trending on Artstation triadic colors Unreal Engine 5 volumetric lighting, spectacular pose, все тело, cinematic beautiful lighting, beautiful colors, highest quality, depth of field, wallpaper, fine details, hyper detail, studio glibli —niji 5</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_8_text">Photo of a ultra realistic horse lying on the ground, dramatic light, pale sunrise, cinematic lighting, beautifuk, low angle, trending on artstation, 4k, hyper realistic, focused, extreme details, unreal engine 5, cinematic, masterpiece, art by studio ghibli, intricate artwork by john william turner</string>
    <string name="item_edit_input_9_text">hyper realistic Slavic happy woman with blond wavy hair, plump lips, blue eyes, a wreath of cornflowers, cranberries, clover and rye on the head, sun, sunny, rays , watercolor pastel effect, dancing in the field of rye Belarusian white national costume</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_10_text">a woman in a red dress walking down a runway, fur cape, elize theron, artforum, fernand keller, sony a 7 iii, gettyimages, dezeen, legend of the cryptids, charlize, peter murbacher, cannes, awe-inspiring. award-winning, fabrics and textiles, soft smoke, armani —relax —v 5.2 —ar 3:4 Detailed photogtaphy a women sit in surrounded by angels, matthias haker, domestic scenes, suspended/hanging, decopunk, lively tableaus, ultra sharp, captured by Hasselblad camera, ultra realistic, style raw</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_11_text">Detailed photogtaphy a women sit in surrounded by angels, matthias haker, domestic scenes, suspended/hanging, decopunk, lively tableaus, ultra sharp, captured by Hasselblad camera, ultra realistic, style raw</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_12_text">drew luther in oblivion, 20142014 b art project photography bsc photography d, in the style of sandra chevrier, elaborate kimono, joachim beuckelaer, photorealistic detail, american prints 1880–1950, light bronze and indigo —ar 127:128</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_13_text">a group of women standing on top of a lush green hillside, inspired by Ren Hang, design milk, long black hair, whites, wanderers traveling from afar, trending on artisation, cloning spell, coat pleats, in twin peaks, submarine, by Helen Thomas Dranga, symetry, round-cropped, noire photo</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_14_text">Beautiful gorgeous candid shot of a cute young 24 years old Russian woman, (long stylish layer hair:1.4), (in a Fringe Trim Glitter Mesh Top and tight black jeans bottom with cute natural makeup:1.4), in Paris during Sunset, (RAW, analog, Sony 85mm, award winning glamour photograph, ((best quality)), ((masterpiece)), ((realistic)), radiant light rays, highres, detailed facial features, high detail, sharp focus, aesthetic, extremely detailed, extremely detailed eyes, extremely detailed body, extremely detailed skin, extremely detailed clothes, octane render, photo_(ultra), realistic, post-processing, max detail, realistic shadows, roughness, natural skin texture, real life, ultra realistic, photorealism, photography, 8k uhd, photography, hdr, intricate, elegant, highly detailed, sharp focus, radiant light rays), ((High Detail RAW color Photo, Full Shot, outdoor), toned physique, perfect face, (detailed skin, diffused skin pores), metal, (highly detailed, fine details, intricate), (lens flare:0.5), (bloom:0.5), smog, dust, (badlands:0.8), (observitory:0.7), raytracing, specular lighting, shallow depth of field, photographed on a Sony Alpha 1, 85mm lens, f/1.4 GM, hard focus, smooth, cinematic film still), (flirting with the camera:1.4), center framed, symmetrical, (photorealistic:1.4), ((full body portrait:1.4)), (textured skin, skin pores:1.2), hasselblad, fashion model, Instagram, nsfw</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_15_text">A model wearing flowing, airy dress walking gracefully along a winding path in a lush garden surrounded by blooming flowers and soft sunlight —v 5.2 —ar 3:4</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_16_text">art of fantasy wolf face art, in the style of baroque-inspired sculptures, intricate body-painting, white and blue, white and gold, sci-fi anime, junglecore, fujifilm x-t4</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_17_text">vogue, high fashion, 1952</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_18_text">a beautiful girl with an office jacket and bra portrait, realistic shaded, fine details, realistically shaded lighting poster by Greg Rutkowski, Magali Villeneuve, art germ, Jeremy Lipkin and Michael garmash, and rob Rey</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_1_text">dynamic angle, dynamic shot, (((masterpiece:1 0))), (hyperrealism:1 5), High Detail RAW color Photo, (full body:1 0), Stunning young model, (italian: 0. 3, Celtic, :0. 3, Romanian:1 4), beautiful girl, model girl, 21 years old, seductive grin, smokey eye shadow, high detail skin, high detail eyes, seductive eyes, smokey makeup, wild dark hair, ((Paris fashion show)), modelling, Summer Dress Collection, stage lighting, photography, bokeh, beautiful dramatic lighting, shallow depth of field, photorealism, volumetric lighting, Ultra HD</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_2_text">dynamic angle, dynamic shot, (((masterpiece:1 0))), (hyperrealism:1 5), High Detail RAW color Photo, (full body:1 0), Stunning young model, (italian: 0. 3, Celtic, :0. 3, Romanian:1 4), beautiful girl, model girl, 21 years old, seductive grin, smokey eye shadow, high detail skin, high detail eyes, seductive eyes, smokey makeup, wild dark hair, ((Paris fashion show)), modelling, Summer Dress Collection, stage lighting, photography, bokeh, beautiful dramatic lighting, shallow depth of field, photorealism, volumetric lighting, Ultra HD</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_3_text">hollywood, standing, wearing a stetson, perfect eyes, perfect face, colorized, actor man, handsome, 1950</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_4_text">a woman in a black dress posing for a picture, italian beach scene, small blond goatee, eighties look, dolce gabbana campaign, alluring face with full makeup, wearing dress, paolo veronese style, photo still of, 18 years old , from italica, ameera al taweel, long luxurious light blond hair, old photobook, aged photo, young</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_5_text">Riley reid, full body, (highly detailed :1.5), (((highly detailed police jacket))), (( Highly detailed police mini tightskirt)),((Lightly curled midle black hair, blue eyes)), (kawaii: 1.5), (detailed cloth fabric: 1.4), (detailed embroidery, long boots: 1.4) , (vividity: 1.3), (striped shirt: 1.2), (face detail: 1.3), (eye detail: 1.3), (hair detail: 1.3),leaning against a building , downtown</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_6_text">davis bowie as a male vampire, surreal masterpiece of a gothic vampire, angry, gothic enchanted (adorned zentangled :1. 1), rotated pose glimpsing, translucent mesh, room made of blood, photo from front down low, drippy wet, vampire teeth, raining blood, dark, canon 85mm f1,2, bokeh, cyborg arm, smirk, mad, perfect face, mouth shut, perfect eyes, perefect hands, fangs, with female horde, hands in fists, hotness</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_7_text">vogue, high fashion, 1952</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_8_text">Kodak disposable photography of Dior boutique popup store, built with crystal, modern, minimalism, 8k, photo realism, —ar 3:4 future fashion, hair styles</string>
    <string name="item_fashion_9_text">future fashion, hair styles</string>
    <string name="item_hd_10_text">Photo of a cartoon-like penguin with a top hat that is on the roof of a building abandoned with vegetation, watching the sunset that can be seen on the horizon. In pixel art style.</string>
    <string name="item_hd_11_text">a beautiful girl face wearing sunglasses and red lipstick, a lifelike portrait with every pore and strand of hair visible, Combine multiple images to create a surreal and visually stunning composition, art nouveau.</string>
    <string name="item_hd_12_text">a realistic vintage car adorned with an intricate, graffiti-style mural, full wide view, highly detailed, 8</string>
    <string name="item_hd_13_text">The image features a stunningly beautiful young France girl who is talking on her cell phone while standing on the street. She is wearing a white top. She is also wearing jeans and glasses, and she is smiling as she engages in her phone conversation. (controlnet_mode:canny, juggernautXL_v5, sdxl-1. 0. 0. 9. safetensors, SeargeSDXL4.1-Llama2 prompt generator)</string>
    <string name="item_hd_14_text">The picture features a 18 years of girl wearing a suit and tie, standing in front of a wall. She is posing for the camera, and her outfit includes a white shirt and a red tie. The woman appears to be confident and well-dressed, possibly for a professional or formal occasion. The image is in black and white, which adds a classic and timeless feel to the scene. (controlnet_mode:canny, juggernautXL_v5, sdxl-1. 0. 0. 9. safetensors, SeargeSDXL4.1-Llama2 prompt generator)</string>
    <string name="item_hd_15_text">Beautiful girl fitness trainer, stands and shows her perfect figure to her full height, well - developed body, beautiful body, athletic legs and hips, colorful realism, epic light, modularity, Highest quality, perfect masterpiece, perfect art, 8K,young and energetic girl, cyberpunk, fashion trends, 3s material, HD, detail performance, ray tracing, complex details, animated lighting, OCrenderer, 8k,</string>
    <string name="item_hd_1_text">A photo of a beautiful cyborg female angel, with expressionless facial features, heavenly, long blonde hair, white armor, melancholy, dynamic lighting, dark background, &lt;lora:ClassipeintXL1.9:1&gt;</string>
    <string name="item_hd_2_text">a woman with tattoos and piercings wearing a black shirt, a 3D render by Sam Spratt, cgsociety, photorealism, daz3d, zbrush, rendered in maya</string>
    <string name="item_hd_3_text">a woman in a shiny jacket posing for a picture, cyberpunk art by Lü Ji, trending on cg society, retrofuturism, glowing neon, futuristic, synthwave</string>
    <string name="item_hd_4_text">studio lighting, film, movie scene, extreme detail, 12k, masterpiece, hyperrealistic, realistic, Peter Quill (Chris Pratt) from Guardians of the Galaxy holding an infinity stone, glowing eyes, powerful shot, Canon EOS R6 Mark II, depth of field, mystical purple particles floating in the air, swirls of power, small purple gem</string>
    <string name="item_hd_5_text">female wolf character portrait with long hair and a large eye, in the style of sculptural costumes, solarization effect, light white and light indigo, matte photo, photo-realistic techniques, fawncore, monochromatic white figures, detailed matte painting, deep color, fantastical, intricate detail, splash screen, complementary colors, fantasy concept art, 8k resolution trending on Artstation Unreal Engine 5</string>
    <string name="item_hd_6_text">a man in a helmet with a dragon on his head, an airbrush painting by Raymond Swanland, featured on zbrush central, fantasy art, reimagined by industrial light and magic, detailed painting, behance hd</string>
    <string name="item_hd_7_text">Rem, Re:Zero, head and shoulders portrait, 8k resolution concept art portrait by Greg Rutkowski, Artgerm, WLOP, Alphonse Mucha dynamic lighting hyperdetailed intricately detailed Splash art trending on Artstation triadic colors Unreal Engine 5 volumetric lighting, spectacular pose, все тело, cinematic beautiful lighting, beautiful colors, highest quality, depth of field, wallpaper, fine details, hyper detail, studio glibli —niji 5</string>
    <string name="item_hd_8_text">Photo of a ultra realistic horse lying on the ground, dramatic light, pale sunrise, cinematic lighting, beautifuk, low angle, trending on artstation, 4k, hyper realistic, focused, extreme details, unreal engine 5, cinematic, masterpiece, art by studio ghibli, intricate artwork by john william turner</string>
    <string name="item_hd_9_text">hyper realistic Slavic happy woman with blond wavy hair, plump lips, blue eyes, a wreath of cornflowers, cranberries, clover and rye on the head, sun, sunny, rays , watercolor pastel effect, dancing in the field of rye Belarusian white national costume</string>
    <string name="item_trending_10_text">Amidst the heart of a mystical enchanted forest ancient trees with gnarled branches stretch towards the heavens| leaves shimmer with an otherworldly iridescence| casting an enchanting glow on the mossy undergrowth| air is perfumed with the scent of blooming| Illuminated by the dappled sunlight| magic pulses in the very air you breathe| inviting you to explore its secrets and unlock the wonders that dwell within 250Create</string>
    <string name="item_trending_11_text">Dynamic angle,(((masterpiece:1 0))),(hyperrealism:1 5),High Detail RAW color Photo,(full body:1 0),Stunning young girl,(italian: 0. 3, Celtic, :0. 3, Romanian:1 4),beautiful girl,model girl,21 years old,seductive grin,smokey eye shadow,high detail skin,high detail eyes,seductive eyes,smokey makeup,wild dark hair,Wavy Cut with Curtain Bangs,high detail hair,long wavy hair,slender body,toned body,perfect face,slim athletic body,(perky small breasts:0.75),((is a Roman Centurion)),Roman Villa,River olive Trees,ancient rome,aquaduct,detailed clothing,intricate clothing,action pose,looking at camera,motion,beautiful digital artworkatmospheric,warm sunlight,photography,neo noir,bokeh,beautiful dramatic lighting,shallow depth of field,photorealism,volumetric lighting,Ultra HD,raytracing,studio quality,octane render,</string>
    <string name="item_trending_12_text">light natural tones , pencil drawing , watercolor drawing, portrait of a woman with long curly hair and white shirt, detailed eyes, beautiful , highly detailed, soft color tones, soft lighting, detailed lines, sharp, realistic, brush strokes, light hints of paint drips</string>
    <string name="item_trending_13_text">ultimate-detailed, masterpiece ,best quality, (photorealistic:1.2),(Pink swimwear:1.2),1girl on Vietnamese beach, beautiful face, (hourglass:1.2),Long hair, smile, looking at viewer,(full body:1.4),earrings, bracelet,(from below:1.2),</string>
    <string name="item_trending_14_text">Drawn by WLOP and Artgerm , ((full body shot, )) portrait, curvy 1girl , tan lines, wavy blonde hair, pale skin, cellulite, micro bikini, blissful look, goosebumps, highlights in eyes, A fantasy, shimmering waterfall amongst strange magical flowers, birds, night time, sparkling fairy lights (((rain ,mist , haze, ))) visible light rays, ethereal, beautiful face, (looking at viewer:1.2), (detailed pupils:1.3), Smooth focus, blurred background, dynamic composition, dynamic lighting, realistic proportions, 16k resolution, ultra realistic,</string>
    <string name="item_trending_15_text">(masterpiece, best quality:1.5), 1girl, solo, Velma of Scooby Doo in sexy outfit, pictorial, curvy body, with tattoos, simple background, uhd image, vibrant illustrations, ultra-realistic, in the style of niji3d,</string>
    <string name="item_trending_16_text">Female shinobi looking back, shot from behind, masked, visible long black hair, with katana, dark padded outfit with leather and metallic accessories, black and red, dark tones, muted colors, high contrast, hyperrealism, black backdrop, minimal lighting.</string>
    <string name="item_trending_17_text">Fashion photo of a woman wearing pink hair in a pink lace dress, in the style of hyperrealism and photorealism, warm lighting, volumetric lighting, UHD image, soft-focused realism, pastel color, babycore 750</string>
    <string name="item_trending_18_text">Heroine of Sleepy Hollow, magical fantasy art is done in oil paint and liquid chrome, liquid gold, liquid black, liquid rainbow, splattered paint, two parts in one art, double exposure, best quality, dark tales, art on a cracked paper, fairytale, patchwork, stained glass, storybook detailed illustration, cinematic, ultra highly detailed, tiny details, beautiful details, mystical, luminism, vibrant colors, complex background, resolution hyperdetailed intricate liminal eerie precisionism, DSLR filmic hyperdetailed, intricate background, fantasy creepy nightmare, dark luminescent art by Tim Burton, Alyssa Monks, Brian Froud, Arthur Rackham, Jean Baptiste Monge, Alberto Seveso, Jeremy Mann, Gris Grimly</string>
    <string name="item_trending_1_text">a painting of a woman, a close-up of a woman face with a mosaic design on it, a mosaic design based on splash colors, vibrant, classic, highly saturated.</string>
    <string name="item_trending_2_text">masterpiece, Rogue assassin girl, wearing a hood, blonde hair, shrouded in shadows, holding a flaming dagger in each hand, vibrant glowing abyssal colors, entirely in frame, FULL BODY, radiating electrical energy, shoulder length messy hair, Full body, Beautiful anime waifu style girl, hyperdetailed painting, luminism, art by Carne Griffiths and Wadim Kashin concept art, 8k resolution, fractal isometrics details bioluminescence , 3d render, octane render, intricately detailed , cinematic, trending on art station Isometric Centered hyper realistic cover photo awesome full color, hand drawn , gritty, realistic, intricate, hit definition , cinematic, Rough sketch, bold lines, on paper, vibrant, epic, ultra high quality model</string>
    <string name="item_trending_3_text">tarot card with intricate detailed frame around the outside | side profile of cyberpunk body with cyborg skull | cyberpunk | styled in Art Nouveau | insanely detailed | embellishments | high definition | concept art | digital art | vibrant</string>
    <string name="item_trending_4_text">she is a gorgeous woman-like being created out smoke ((she is coming out of a sunset mist), smoke dances around the character, by Vladimir Matyukhin, RAW, intricate, vibrant colors, (((facing viewer)))</string>
    <string name="item_trending_5_text">Insane portrait digital painting of The Joker, the dark night rises, action rage pose, with a beautiful white tiger by his side, vivid, colorful, bright color schemes, artistic flare, highly detailed</string>
    <string name="item_trending_6_text">Classic traditional cornucopia at the fall harvest festival, farm in the background, high quality masterful still-life painting, American pastoral, oil painting, festive spirit, vibrant cultural tradition, Autumnal atmosphere, vibrant rich colors, atmospheric perspective, depth, beautiful amazing composition, illustration, intricate details, ultra high resolution, sharp details, sharp focus, 8k resolution</string>
    <string name="item_trending_7_text">masterpiece, (beautiful and aesthetic:1. 5), surrealism, highly detailed, a portrait painting of 1girl with orange and blue color pallet, hard brush, minimalist low poly collage illustration, splatter oil paintings effect, city portraits, heavy inking,Create</string>
    <string name="item_trending_8_text">betty page as ahorror creature from Space. terraforming. Alien Flora, large gazing eyes, close-up, hyper detailed, rich colours, red green, rich dark shadows, yellow, bioluminescent, colourfull, glow, fluid slime glowingslobber, oozing, dripping, moist, fleshy, trending on artstation, sharp focus, studio photo, intricate details, highly detailed, glossy, slimy, mucous, by greg rutkowski detailed face, detailed skin</string>
    <string name="item_trending_9_text">By Tang Yau Hoong, ultra hd, realistic, vivid colors, highly detailed, UHD drawing, pen and ink, perfect composition, beautiful detailed intricate insanely detailed octane render trending on artstation, 8k artistic photography, photorealistic concept art, soft natural volumetric cinematic perfect light, ultra hd, realistic, vivid colors, highly detailed, UHD drawing, pen and ink, perfect composition, beautiful detailed intricate insanely detailed octane render trending on artstation, 8k artistic photography, photorealistic concept art, soft natural volumetric cinematic perfect lightCreate</string>
    <string name="realistic_vision">Realistic Vision</string>
    <string name="stable_diffusion">Stable Diffusion</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="item_10_text">gorgeous 2b by ilya kuvshinov, krenz cushart, Greg Rutkowski, trending on artstation</string>
    <string name="item_11_text">magical fairy floating in space, epic cartoon portrait made out of rain, beautiful face, stunning concept art, highly detailed, galaxy background, rendered in octane, unreal engine, trending on artstation, realistic, diviantart</string>
    <string name="item_12_text">portrait of a classy curvy pale goth woman with an elaborate elegant silver multilayered latex high-neck outfit, cgsociety, photorealistic, sublime, cool, 16k, smooth, sharp focus, trending on ArtStation, volumetric lighting</string>
    <string name="item_13_text">portrait of blonde girl with mutiple heads, jump suit, vivid eyes, real life skin, intricate, elegant, highly detailed, artstation, concept art, smooth, sharp focus, art by artgerm and greg rutkowski and alphonse mucha</string>
    <string name="item_14_text">sword inspired by a kingfisher, deep focus, d&amp;d, fantasy, intricate, elegant, highly detailed, digital painting, artstation, concept art, matte, sharp focus, illustration, hearthstone, art by artgerm and greg rutkowski and alphonse mucha</string>
    <string name="item_15_text">a photo of yoda holding a green balloon in the tokyo suburbs by wes anderson, highly detailed, trending on artstation</string>
    <string name="item_16_text">by kyoto animation, very creepy clown girl, wearing cyberpunk intricate streetwear, beautiful, detailed portrait, intricate complexity, ilya kuvshinov, cell shaded, 4k, concept art, by wlop, ilya kuvshinov, artgerm, krenz cushart, greg rutkowski, sharp focus, volumetric lighting, cinematic lighting, studio quality</string>
    <string name="item_17_text">Hyper realistic detailed portrait of Kurdish samurai, Stephen Bliss, unreal engine, fantasy art by Greg Rutkowski, Loish, Rhads, ferdinand knab, Makoto Shinkai and Lois van baarle, ilya kuvshinov, rossdraws, Tom Bagshaw, alphonse mucha, global illumination, radiant light, detailed and intricate environment, highly detailed, award winning art</string>
    <string name="item_18_text">cute friendly fantasy goblin wrapped in bandages by charlie bowater and titian and artgerm, intricate, face, forest, elegant, green mist, beautiful, highly detailed, dramatic lighting, sharp focus, trending on artstation, artstationhd, artstationhq, unreal engine, 4k, 8k</string>
    <string name="item_19_text">full body shot of dark elf witch, highly detailed, d&amp;d, fantasy, highly detailed, digital painting, trending on artstation, concept art, sharp focus, illustration, global illumination, ray tracing, realistic shaded, art by artgerm and greg rutkowski and fuji choko and viktoria gavrilenko and hoang lap,</string>
    <string name="item_1_text">digital character concept art by artgerm and greg rutkowski and alphonse mucha. avocado dragon, beautiful, holding a stuff, detailed, poster art, light effect, glowing, hyper detail, intricate, elegant, digital painting, artstation, smooth, sharp focus</string>
    <string name="item_20_text">portrait of a cute white long haired anime foxgirl in a forest, detailed face, highly detailed, sharp focus, trending on artstation, art by Krenz Cushart and Ross Tran</string>
    <string name="item_21_text">cinematic bust portrait of a green frog from left, head and chest only, exotic alien features, robotic enhancements, desaturated, tim hildebrandt, wayne barlowe, bruce pennington, donato giancola, larry elmore, oil on canvas, masterpiece, trending on artstation, featured on pixiv, cinematic composition, dramatic pose, beautiful lighting, sharp, details, hyper-detailed, hd, hdr, 4k, 8k</string>
    <string name="item_22_text">wolf gangs wear gray bandana, other people use wolf mask. pop art, pixel, bioshock infinite art style, gta chinatown wars art style, dynamic proportional, dynamic composition, face features, body features, ultra realistic art, digital painting, concept art, smooth, sharp focus, illustration, intricate, without duplication, elegant, confident posse, art by artgerm and richard hamilton and mimmo rottela</string>
    <string name="item_23_text">lee jin-eun wearing luxurious dress emerging from pink water with cyberpunk theme by greg rutkowski, claude monet, conrad roset, takato yomamoto, rule of thirds, seductive look, beautiful, sakura flowers, dreamy,</string>
    <string name="item_24_text">the bright light looking at you with a blured snapshot of the universe in the background fromlost in space ( 2018 ) , soft muted flares on backside, frontal view, very long shot, cinematic light, realistic shaded lighting, futuristic, digital art, trending on artstation, golden ratio, perfect symmetrical, perfect intricate, masterpiece, hyperrealistic, octane render</string>
    <string name="item_25_text">ultra realistic illustration, deanna troi as persephone, intricate, elegant, highly detailed, digital painting, artstation, concept art, smooth, sharp focus, illustration, art by artgerm and greg rutkowski and alphonse mucha</string>
    <string name="item_26_text">an angelic white dragon, highly detailed, digital painting, artstation, concept art, sharp focus, illustration, art by greg rutkowski and alphonse mucha</string>
    <string name="item_27_text">an anthropomorphic beautiful goddess skull wizard portrait wearing batik robe in a desert, round glasses, fine art, award winning, intricate, elegant, sharp focus, octane render, hyperrealistic, cinematic lighting, highly detailed, digital painting, 8k concept art, art by jamie hewlett and z. w. gu, masterpiece, trending on artstation, 8k</string>
    <string name="item_28_text">Anthropomorphic female salamander healer with a glowing potion in her hand, DnD character, unreal engine, octane render, dramatic lighting, pond, digital art, by Stanley Artgerm Lau, greg rutkowski, thomas kindkade, alphonse mucha, loish, norman Rockwell</string>
    <string name="item_29_text">portrait of a ranni from elden ring, baroque style, elegant, beautiful, mesmerizing, concept art, fancy clothing, highly detailed, artstation, behance, deviantart, inspired by innocent manga, inspired by castlevania concept art, trending, ayami kojima, shinichi sakamoto</string>
    <string name="item_2_text">the photo of pregnant three-headed dog and priest, bright color, dripping salvia, horror, 3D, high details, by vincent di fate, artgerm julie bell beeple, 90s, octane render, 8K, volumetric lighting, high contract, duo tone, depth of field, very coherent symmetrical artwork</string>
    <string name="item_30_text">Group of aliens chilling on the moon smoking weed, gritty space atmosphere realistic digital art 4K, high quality, Greg Rutkowski, Zabrocki, Karlkka, Jayison Devadas, Phuoc Quan, trending on Artstation, 8K, ultra wide angle, zenith view, pincushion lens effect</string>
    <string name="item_31_text">three quarters portrait of a cute baby werewolf with big glowing eyes, highly detailed, digital painting, dark retrowave, art by Stanley Lau and Artgerm and magali villeneuve and Alphonse Mucha, artstation, octane render, cgsociety</string>
    <string name="item_32_text">Naturecore Trust by Joe Jusko, rendered in hyperdetailed Ultra HD, trending on ArtStation, luminous</string>
    <string name="item_33_text">a majestic steampunk alchemists spinning ornate globe, furniture, high details, bold line art, by vincent di fate and joe fenton, inking, etching, screen print, masterpiece, trending on artstation, sharp, high contrast, hyper-detailed,, hd, 4k, 8k</string>
    <string name="item_34_text">a girl playing on a fighting game controller by krenz cushart stu_dts yoshiku wlop trending on ArtStation Pixiv</string>
    <string name="item_35_text">wonderland dreamscape faeries lady forest feather wing digital art painting fantasy bloom snyder zack and swanland raymond and pennington bruce illustration character design co</string>
    <string name="item_36_text">female lawyer, business suit, brown neat hairr, pixiv, fanbox, trending on artstation, digital painting, defense attorney, modern, sleek, highly detailed, formal, serious, determined, competent</string>
    <string name="item_37_text">a closeup photorealistic photograph of a Louis Vuitton themed bichon frise at the beach during sunset This 4K HD image is Trending on Artstation, featured on Behance, well-rendered, extra crisp, features intricate detail and the style of Unreal Engine.</string>
    <string name="item_38_text">green kitten on ground, intricate, highly detailed, artstation, sharp focus, illustration, jurgens, rutkowski, mucha</string>
    <string name="item_39_text">!!!angled facial portrait of a cyberpunk bone ceramic caliente humanoid robot Brasileiro with an attractive face and handsome features, large white glowing eyes, macho, piroca, dotado, guapo, reflective surface, trending on cgsociety, trending on artstation</string>
    <string name="item_3_text">a hyperrealistic painting of a human cyborg with cables coming out from his limbs connected to supercomputers, flood of images flowing from his head, tesseract, by greg rutkowski, artgerm, yakihiko yoshida and beeple, trending on artstation, concept art, insane details, zoomed out</string>
    <string name="item_40_text">the goddess of the lake, stand in the middle of lake, halo in the hand, highly detailed, d&amp;d, water everywhere, rainbow across the lake, fantasy, highly detailed, digital painting, trending on artstation, concept art, sharp focus, global illumination, ray tracing, illustration, art by artgerm and greg rutkowski and fuji choko and viktoria gavrilenko and hoang lap</string>
    <string name="item_41_text">high quality 3d render cyberpunk very cute pastel fluffy! quokka cyborg, highly detailed, vray smooth, in the style of detective pikachu, hannah yata charlie immer, dramatic blue light, low angle, uhd 8k, sharp focus</string>
    <string name="item_42_text">((portrait of young girl playing with a white bunny)), (best friends for life), (Alice In Wonderland), (long floating hair), {blue eyes}, wearing cute gown, (((magical mushroom forest))), moss, flowers, clovers, (((stunning breathtaking background))), sunlight, dreamy atmosphere, (fantasy), intricate, highly detailed, sharp focus, (((ultra wide angle))), ((eye level perspective)), ((low angle shot)), (centered image composition), professionally color graded, masterpiece, trending on artstation, hdr 4k, 8k, ((samdoesarts))</string>
    <string name="item_43_text">a visual stunning photo of a kitsune | glowing | cyberpunk city | neon light | vibrant | Full body| key visual | highly detailed| breathtaking beauty | comprehensive cinematic | dynamic fighting pose | best quality| ultra sharp focus| cinematic lighting, volumetric fog, bioluminescence, volumetric atmosphere, studio trigger Military style Knee pads, , UHD, HDR, 16K, (Masterpiece:1. 5) Model: ReV Animated</string>
    <string name="item_44_text">(Cinematic illumination, insane, stunning, dramatic), Award winning splash art of a cute fluffy cat wearing and suit and bowtie (sitting:1. 1) on a magical toadstool in an( enchanted mushroom forest:1. 1) in the (style-sylvamagic), ( intricate details:1. 2), beautiful eyes, sunlight, (high quality:1. 2), trending on artstation, absurdres, (close up:1. 1) (from side:1. 1)</string>
    <string name="item_45_text">A beautiful cute indian girl hugging a horse face</string>
    <string name="item_46_text">The image features a woman wearing a black top and a blue hat with a feather. She is also wearing a pair of earrings, which adds to her elegant appearance. The woman is posing for a picture, and her gaze is directed towards the camera. The overall scene is a portrait of a stylish and confident woman. (controlnet_mode:canny sdxlYamersRealism2, sdxl-1.0.0.9.safetensors, SeargeSDXL4.2-Llama2 prompt)</string>
    <string name="item_47_text">Character of the game, villainess Annie is a child firemage with immense pyromantic power, summoning of her beloved massive scale teddy bear Tibbers, as a fiery guardian. Portrait by Gustave Moreau, Thomas Kinkade, James Gurney. Carne Griffiths. Frank Frazetta. Alberto Seveso, oil paint, masterpiece, Realistic, deep colors, Field, Intricate, detailed, sharp, clear, Perfect face, Red hair, Focus on the face, clear eyes. Better image quality</string>
    <string name="item_48_text">Abstract interpretation of Mickey Mouse, vibrant colors, Jackson Pollock-inspired backdrop, full image splash, feature in MoMA magazine, Pixabay, wild, emotional, high art, impressionism, 3D model, Maya, color-spattered face and body, high-resolution texture, 4k, professional photography, award winning artwork</string>
    <string name="item_49_text">a bear is in space suit, standing in the dirt, in the style of fantasy art, dark white and dark orange, poodlepunk, flickr, charming characters, marine painter, hd --ar 10:13</string>
    <string name="item_4_text">Naturecore Trust by Joe Jusko, rendered in hyperdetailed Ultra HD, trending on ArtStation, luminous</string>
    <string name="item_50_text">Two babies in hollows of trees, in the style of hyperrealistic wildlife portraits, avian - themed, stephen shortridge, lilia alvarado, bob eggleton, detailed wildlife, nature studies --ar 53:89 --q 2 --s 750 --style raw</string>
    <string name="item_51_text">cyberpunk cute mechanic cat, futuristic, highly detailed, made with blender, unreal engine, volumetric lighting, white background --s 750 --q 2</string>
    <string name="item_52_text">lion and his cubs, in the style of nikon d850, combining natural and man-made elements, colorized, jessica drossin, alasdair mclellan, pristine naturalism, powerful symbolism, ultra-detailed, highest detail quality, ultra-realistic, photorealistic, cinematic, movie quality rendering, octane rendering, focused, depth of field, real shadow, vfx post-production, rtx ray tracing lighting, 32k uhd, --ar 160:159 --quality 2 --s 750 --v 5. 1</string>
    <string name="item_53_text">portrait of beautiful faerie with butterfly wings, headshot, symmetrical, elegant, regal, intricate, fireflies in a twilight background, highly detailed, digital painting, artstation, concept art, sharp focus, watercolor ink illustration, muted color, complementary colors, art by artgerm, bastien lechouffe deharme, greg rutkowski and alphonse mucha</string>
    <string name="item_54_text">Beautiful mermaid on a lake, wet and dense, mysterious, siren, unholy, creepy, horror, dark, intricate design and details, dramatic lighting, photorealistic, cinematic, 8k --ar 9:16 --v 5</string>
    <string name="item_5_text">an art nouveau realistic illustration of a cat lying on her bed wearing an holographic kimono designed by balenciaga by john berkey by stanley artgerm lau, greg rutkowski, thomas kinkade, alphonse mucha, loish, norman rockwell</string>
    <string name="item_6_text">Group of aliens chilling on the moon smoking weed, gritty space atmosphere realistic digital art 4K, high quality, Greg Rutkowski, Zabrocki, Karlkka, Jayison Devadas, Phuoc Quan, trending on Artstation, 8K, ultra wide angle, zenith view, pincushion lens effect</string>
    <string name="item_7_text">highly realistic boy with curly brown hair and brown eyes, a wooden bow on his back, highly detailed and intricate, concept art illustration</string>
    <string name="item_8_text">highly detailed vfx portrait of nico robin by eiichiro oda, makoto shinkai, alphonse mucha, sharp focus, art by artgerm and greg rutkowski!, backlit, harsh overhead sunlight, blue eyes, aquiline nose, stanley kybric, kaoru mori, hyper detailed, smooth pixiv, fanbox,</string>
    <string name="item_9_text">Portrait of Jean Luc Picard &amp; Kirk wearing spacesuits, real life skin, intricate, elegant, highly detailed, artstation, concept art, smooth, sharp focus, art by artgerm and greg rutkowski and alphonse mucha</string>
    <string name="vibrant">VIBRANT</string>

</resources>